Guide to the International Center for Transitional Justice (ICTJ) records, 1918-2020, bulk 1970-2020 RL.01304
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Program and Subject Files, 1979-2015
  - Subject Area Files, 1985-2014
    - Gender: Audiovisual Materials
      - Live Containers, 2002; VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0082)
        Gender Montage: Paradigms in Post Soviet Space, Tajikistan
      - No es solo mi problema es de todo mi pueblo: mujeres victimas de violación sexual durante el conflicto armado interno, 2003; VHS (Box 123, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0023)
      - Power: Feminine Gender, 2003; VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0084)
        Gender Montage: Paradigms in Post Soviet Space, Ukraine
      - Red Butterflies Where Two Springs Merge, 2002; VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0083)
        Gender Montage: Paradigms in Post Soviet Space, Kyrgyzstan
      - Silk Patterns, 2003; VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0087)
        Gender Montage: Paradigms in Post Soviet Space, Mongolia
      - Tomorrow Will Be Better?, 2003; VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0085)
        Gender Montage: Paradigms in Post Soviet Space, Lithuania
      - Wishing for Seven Sons and One Daughter, 2002; VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0080)
        Gender Montage: Paradigms in Post Soviet Space, Azerbaijan
    - Genocide, 2006-2007; 2 folders (Box 87)
      Minority Rights Group International report on preventing genocide, crisis in Darfur.
    - Genocide: Audiovisual Materials
      Series of videos on the Holocaust in Spanish.
      - Holocausto I: El Silencio de la Verdad, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0151)
      - Holocausto II: El Legado de las Justos I, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0152)
      - Holocausto III: El Legado de las Justos II, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0153)
      - Holocausto IV: Un Prologo para la Historia, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0154)
    - Human Rights (General), 1985-2013; 20 folders (Box 87)
      Human rights defenders, human rights reform, human rights and the interests of justice, Human Rights Council reports, Basic Handbook for Human Rights, transitional justice mapping, Bosnian Book of the Dead database report.
    - Human Rights (General): Audiovisual Materials
      - Instituto Interamericano de Derechos Humanos; Systems to protect human rights, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0178)
    - International Criminal Court (ICC), 2000-2011; 39 folders (Box 87-88)
      ICC Monitor, ICC Coalition, Insight newsletter, ICC information packets, ICC Coalition members, ICC Victims Rights Working Group, Victims and Witness Unit, Trust Fund for Victims, Prosecution and the ICC, ICC Rome Statute, Commentary on the Rome Statute, selection of the Planet OTP Bulletin.
    - International Human Rights Law, 1991-2007; 13 folders (Box 88)
      Holocaust restitution, OCHA Human Rights Law, sanctions, war crimes statute of limitations, universal jurisdiction.
    - Legal Issues/Rule of Law, 2002-2011; 11 folders (Box 88)
      Rule of law in post conflict countries, integrated approach to rule of law, IDEELE publications for the Institute for Legal Defense, UN OHCHR "Rule of Law in Post-Conflict States," OSI Legal Institute.
    - Legal Issues/Rule of Law: Audiovisual Materials
      - 18 Ensayos Justicia Transicional, Estado de Derecho, y Democracia, 2005; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0029)
      - 18 Ensayos Justicia Transicional, Estado de Derecho, y Democracia, 2005; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0032)
      - 18 Ensayos Justicia Transicional, Estado de Derecho, y Democracia, 2005; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0033)
      - 18 Ensayos Justicia Transicional, Estado de Derecho, y Democracia, 2005; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0034)
    - Memory and Truth, 1994-2014; 20 folders (Box 88-89)
      Truth seeking articles, Right to Truth project, Truth and Memory meeting, Managing Truth Commissions (MTC) meetings, Historical Memory project, naming and transitional justice, memorials.
    - Memory and Truth: Audiovisual Materials
      - Art of Truth Telling, 2004 April; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0077)
      - Art of Truth Telling (book), 2004 April; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0078)
      - Centro de Información para la Memoria Colectiva y los Derechos Humanos, CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0038)
        Defensoria del Pueblo (Peru)
      - Centro de Información para la Memoria Colectiva y los Derechos Humanos, CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0039)
    - Post-conflict/Peacebuilding/Peacekeeping/Reconciliation, 1991-2014; 81 folders (Box 89-91)
      FRIDE report on recovering from armed conflict, UN and EU peacebuilding, Lawyers Without Borders publications, protection of victims and witnesses, UN Peacebuilding Commission, transitional justice articles, transitional justice working group, vetting case studies and project proposal, disarmament, demobilization and reintegration (DDR).
    - Post-Conflict/Peacebuilding/Peacekeeping/Reconciliation: Audiovisual Materials
      - New Paths for International Justice, VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0178)
        tape 1 of 2
      - New Paths for International Justice, VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0179)
        Tape 2 of 2
      - Humanitarian Crisis, Post Conflict, and Reconciliation Vol 1, 2004; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0011)
      - Humanitarian Crisis, Post Conflict, and Reconciliation Vol 1, 2004; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0012)
      - Humanitarian Crisis, Post Conflict, and Reconciliation Vol 2, 2004; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0013)
      - Humanitarian Crisis, Post Conflict, and Reconciliation Vol 2, 2004; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0014)
      - Humanitarian Crisis, Post Conflict, and Reconciliation Vol 3, 2004; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0015)
    - Prosecutions/International Criminal Tribunals, 2001-2011; 44 folders (Box 91-92)
      Tribunals and the International Commission of Jurists, the historical function of criminal tribunals, model transitional codes for post conflict criminal justice, Redress Trust report on immunity and accountability, interrelationships between criminal prosecutions and truth commissions, Iraqi Criminal Tribunal materials, Extraordinary Chambers of the Courts of Cambodia materials, trying heads of state, peacebuilding workshops, working group on lessons learned.
    - Reparations, 1980-2011; 103 folders (Box 92-94, 144)
      Reparations articles, reparations in: Guatemala, South Africa, Brazil, Malawi, Yugoslavia, Peru, Canada, Colombia, Morocco, Sri Lanka, Germany, Chile, Zimbabwe, Chechnya, reparations and gender.
    - Reparations: Audiovisual Materials
      - Una Experiencia Privada de Investigación Extrajudicial y Reparacion para Víctimas de Tortura, CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0027)
      - Video Reparaciones para pasar Jueves en la tarde, VHS (Box 123, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0020)
        note says it starts at 55 seconds
    - Refugees/Displacement, 2001-2008; 8 folders (Box 94, 144)
      Refugee Studies Center report, Brookings Institute report on risks, rights, and displacement, USAID assistance to internally displaced persons policy, refugee project, ICRC project on the missing, displacement project proposal.
    - Refugees/Displacement: Audiovisual Materials
      - Banished, 2009; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0149)
        Film by Marco Williams
      - Guide to International Human Rights Mechanisms for Internally Displaced Persons and their Advocates, CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0025)
      - Kosovo Missing: the Right to Know, 2001; VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0091)
        ICRC project on the missing
    - Security/Terrorism, 2002-2009; 6 folders (Box 94)
      Terrorism and law, UN high level panel on threats, UN Security Council's Counterterrorism program, Guantanamo Bay article.
    - Truth and Reconciliation Commissions, 1994-2013; 54 folders (Box 95, Box 146, Box 145)
      Truth Commission articles, keeping records of truth commissions, operational guidelines of truth commissions, selection procedures for truth commissions, Derrida Pardon, procedural fairness considerations for truth commissions handbook, truth commissions in: Peru, South Africa, Indonesia, the United States (Greensboro), Mexico, El Salvador, Guatemala, Kenya, Ghana, Uganda, Argentina, Yugoslavia, and Australia.
    - United Nations, 1998-2011; 16 folders (Box 95)
      UN peacekeeping operations, Security Council reports, UN Office of the High Commissioner on Human Rights materials, Responsibility to Protect (R2P), Transparency International recommendations for a UN convention against corruption.
    - United Nations: Audiovisual Materials
      Series of interviews with Special Representatives of the Secretary-General.
      - Interview with Ahmedou Ould-Abdallah Special Representative of the Secretary-General for Burundi, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0058)
        UNITAR Series
      - Interview with Aldo Ajello Special Representative of the Secretary-General for Mozambique, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0047)
      - Interview with Alvaro de Soto Personal Representative of the Secretary-General for the Central American Peace Process, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0050)
      - Interview with Berhanu Dinka Special Representative of the Secretary-General for Burundi, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0051)
      - Interview with David Stephen Special Representative of the Secretary-General for Somalia, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0062)
      - Interview with Dieter Boden Special Representative of the Secretary-General for Georgia, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0049)
      - Interview with Francesc Vendrell Personal Representative of the Secretary-General for Afghanistan, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0063)
      - Interview with Ian Martin Special Representative of the Secretary-General for East Timor, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0056)
      - Interview with Ivo Petrov Special Representative of the Secretary-General for Tajikistan, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0059)
      - Interview with Jan Egland Special Advisor of the Secretary-General for International Assistance to Colombia, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0052)
      - Interview with Jean Arnault Special Representative of the Secretary-General for Guatemala, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0048)
      - Interview with Kamel Morjane Special Representative of the Secretary-General for the Democratic Republic of the Congo, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0057)
      - Interview with Kieran Prendergast Under-Secretary-General for Political Affairs, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0060)
      - Interview with Legwaila Joseph Legwaila Special Representative of the Secretary-General for Ethiopia/Eritrea, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0055)
      - Interview with Michael Jorsback Police Advisor, Department of Peacekeeping Operations, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0054)
      - Interview with Noel Sinclair Head of the United Nations Political Office in Bougainville, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0061)
      - Interview with Oluyemi Adeniji Special Representative of the Secretary-General for Sierra Leone, 2001 November; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0046)
      - Interview with Timothy Ford Military Advisor Department of Peacekeeping Operations, 2002; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0053)
  - ICTJ Programs, 1979-2014
    Contains files of ICTJ program units including the Americas Program, Middle East/North Africa (MENA), Policymakers program, ICTJ Productions, as well as the Truth and Reconciliation Commissions ICTJ assisted with.
    - Americas Program, 2006-2010; 9 folders (Box 96)
      Contains the files of the Americas Program division of ICTJ. The Americas Program's work centers around both North and South American transitional justice issues. Includes Americas Regional meeting, Regional Directors meeting, challenges for transitional justice in the Americas, Country Program Unit (CPU) workplan, Americas Program workplan, Americas Program reports, Americas assistant handover memos.
    - Middle East/North Africa (MENA) Division, 1993-2011; 48 folders (Box 96-98)
      Contains the files of the Middle East/North Africa program division of ICTJ. Includes human rights in the Iraqi Context interview transcripts (22 folders), Iraq Survey project, Human Rights Watch reports, Amnesty International reports, draft notes on the Iraq Report, human rights in Iraq, security logistics, bringing Iraqi provincial leaders to justice, transitional justice and the US occupation in Iraq, Netherlands development in Iraq, Morocco TRC files, publications on Middle East issues, UNDP Arab Human Development report, development and project proposals, MENA workplan, transitional justice in Sudan, establishment of an ICTJ office in Lebanon. Contains materials in Arabic.
    - MENA Electronic Records, 2305 document (Microsoft Word, PDF, and other formats), 641 audiovisual (predominantly MPEG-4 format), 475 still image (TIFF, JPEG, GIF, and PNG formats), and 318 web (predominantly HTML format) files; approximately 178 GB. (Digital-materials RL01304-SET-0006)
      Iraqi High Tribunal documents and videos from MENA.
    - Policymakers Unit, 2003-2007; 10 folders (Box 98)
      Contains files of the Policymakers Unit of ICTJ which focuses on international policy and its role in transitional or truth seeking processes. Reports on a grant from Finland, UN General Reference, workplans, strategic plans, and three year vision, policymaking between ICTJ and the EU, the UN's role in conflict resolution, workshops on amnesty and the rule of law.
    - ICTJ Productions, 2007-2010; 24 folders (Box 98)
      Contains files of ICTJ Productions, established in 2008 to use film and media to tell the stories of individuals and nations coming to terms with an abusive past. Includes Humanity United grant and proposal, Coke/World Cup project, ICTJ productions powerpoint introduction, Zimbabwe materials, Guzman documentary, agreement between the Sundance Institute and ICTJ, community based theater and transitional justice in Afghanistan, ICTJ Productions goals and background, Web Portal project, "And There in the Dust" scripts, scripts and proposals, "Redemption" film about Desmond Tutu, grant agreements.
    - ICTJ Productions Electronic Records, 10 audiovisual files (MP3 and Windows Media Video formats); approximately 0.2 GB. (Digital-materials RL01304-SET-0003)
      ICTJ's work with Pivot Pictures.
    - Truth and Reconciliation Commissions, 1979-2014; 183 folders (Box 98-103, Box 145, Box 146)
      Contains the files of Truth Commissions that ICTJ assisted in conducting. Truth Commissions are defined by ICTJ as "temporary, official inquiries established to determine the facts, causes, and consequences of past human rights violations."
      Arranged alphabetically by country: box 98 Brazil, box 99 Brazil-Peru, box 100 Peru-South Africa, box 101 United States, box 102 United States, box 103 United States-Yugoslavia. Additional materials located in Boxes 145-146.
    - Truth and Reconciliation Commissions: Audiovisual Materials
      - Truth Commissions (General)
        - Hearings Summary, DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0004)
        - Imagining Future Truth Commissions; The Role of Commissioners, DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0026)
        - Strategic Choices in the Design of Truth Commissions, CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0111)
        - Wake-Up Call, 2003-09-05; Cassette (Box 135, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0042)
          Priscilla Hayner and Lisa Magarrell talking about TRCs on WBAI 99.5 FM
        - The Truth Commission, VHS (Box 126, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0125)
        - ICTJ Public Hearings CD, 2005; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0001)
      - Chile
        - 6 spots radiales en castellano y quechua, 2002-03-02; Cassette (Box 134, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0029)
          Chile CVR (Sur Andino region)
        - 15 Spots en Castellano y en Aymara, 2002-03-02; Cassette (Box 134, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0028)
      - Ghana
        - Torture and Brutality in the Security Services of Ghana, 2001; Betacam-sp (Box 130, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0022)
          Ghana NRC
        - Torture and Brutality in the Security Services of Ghana, 2001; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0024)
          Ghana NRC (dubbed from Betamax tapes)
        - Torture and Brutality in the Security Services of Ghana, 2001; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0013)
        - Prime Star: Hearing of the National Reconciliation Commission, VHS (Box 123, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0026)
          Ghana National Reconciliation Commission (series of 7 tapes)
        - Prime Star: Hearing of the National Reconciliation Commission, VHS (Box 123, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0027)
        - Prime Star: Hearing of the National Reconciliation Commission, VHS (Box 123, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0028)
        - Prime Star: Hearing of the National Reconciliation Commission, VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0029)
        - Prime Star: Hearing of the National Reconciliation Commission, VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0030)
        - Prime Star: Hearing of the National Reconciliation Commission, VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0031)
        - Prime Star: Hearing of the National Reconciliation Commission, VHS (Box 124, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0032)
        - Persecution of Civilians by the Military of Ghana, 2001; Betacam-sp (Box 130, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0021)
        - Persecution of Civilians by the Military of Ghana, 2001; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0023)
        - Persecution of Civilians by the Military of Ghana, 2001; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0012)
        - Military Atrocities in Ghana, 2001; Betacam-sp (Box 130, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0018)
        - Military Atrocities in Ghana, 2001; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0009)
        - Mistreatment and Harassment in the Armed Forces of Ghana, 2001; Betacam-sp (Box 130, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0019)
        - Mistreatment and Harassment in the Armed Forces of Ghana, 2001; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0021)
        - Mistreatment and Harassment in the Armed Forces of Ghana, 2001; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0010)
        - Misuse of Power in the Security Services of Ghana, 2001; Betacam-sp (Box 130, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0020)
        - Misuse of Power in the Security Services of Ghana, 2001; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0022)
        - Misuse of Power in the Security Services of Ghana, 2001; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0011)
        - Truth Commission-Ghana; The Role of Commissioners (Spanish); Justice in Transitional Societies Program, DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0027)
          Dubbed from Betamax tapes
        - Women Witnesses at the NRC, 2001; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0014)
        - Women as Protagonists (NTSC 13), 2002-05-22; 2002-09-10; Betacam-sp (Box 129, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0013)
          Peru TCR
        - Women Witnesses at the NRC, 2001; Betacam-sp (Box 130, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0023)
        - Women Witnesses at the NRC, 2001; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0025)
        - ICTJ Truth Commission-Ghana, Betacam (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0025)
        - Ill Treatment and Unlawful Seizure of Property, 2001; Betacam-sp (Box 130, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0017)
        - Ill Treatment and Unlawful Seizure of Property, 2001; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0020)
        - Ill Treatment and Unlawful Seizure of Property, 2001; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0008)
        - Ghana NRC Beta Spillover Tape 1, 2, 9, Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0271)
        - Ghana NRC Beta Spillover Tape 10, Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0272)
        - Ghana NRC Hearings, VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0181)
        - Ghana NRC Hearings, VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0182)
        - ICTJ presents Hearing of the National Reconciliation Commission: Military Atrocities in Ghana, 2001; VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0192)
        - Abduction and the Murder of Judges and Military Officers (part 1), 2001; Betacam-sp (Box 130, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0014)
        - Abduction and the Murder of Judges and Military Officers (part 1), 2001; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0017)
        - Abduction and the Murder of Judges and Military Officers (part 2), 2001; Betacam-sp (Box 130, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0015)
        - Abduction and the Murder of Judges and Military Officers (part 2), 2001; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0018)
        - Abduction and the Murder of Judges and Military Officers (part 2), 2001; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0006)
        - Abuse of Power in the Military of Ghana, 2001; Betacam-sp (Box 130, Video-cassette RL01304-Bcam-0016)
        - Abuse of Power in the Military of Ghana, 2001; DVCAM (Box 131, Video-cassette RL01304-DVCAM-0019)
        - Abuse of Power in the Military of Ghana, 2001; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0007)
      - Guatemala
        - Guatemala Memoria del Silencio, CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0023)
          Guatemalan TRC Final Report
        - Guatemala Memoria del Silencio, CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0024)
        - Guatemala Memoria del Silencio, CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0037)
      - Liberia
        - Information about giving your statement to the Liberian Truth and Reconciliation Commission in the United States, DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0049)
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0308)
          #6 Former President Moses Z. Blah
        - Liberia TRC Workshop, Tape 1, 2006-10-14; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0614)
        - Liberia TRC Workshop, Tape 2, 2006-10-14; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0615)
        - Liberia TRC Workshop, Tape 3, 2006-10-14; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0616)
        - Liberia TRC Workshop, Tape 4, 2006-10-14; Mini-DV (Box 142, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0617)
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0303)
          #1 Former President Moses Z. Blah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0304)
          #2 Former President Moses Z. Blah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0305)
          #3 Former President Moses Z. Blah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0306)
          #4 Former President Moses Z. Blah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0307)
          #5 Former President Moses Z. Blah
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-09-10; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0328)
          #26 Sen. Saye Taryor Adolphus Dolo
        - Liberia Truth and Reconciliation Commission Thematic and Institutional Hearings at the Centennial Pavilion, Monrovia, 2008-08-19; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0317)
          #15 Lewis G. Brown